## Mr. Sukhrob Ilyosbekov

Age: 21

Nationality: Uzbekistan

Email address: <a href="mailto:suxrobGM@gmail.com">suxrobGM@gmail.com</a>
Web: <a href="http://www.suxrobgm.net">http://www.suxrobgm.net</a>

Facebook: <a href="https://www.facebook.com/suxrobgm">https://www.facebook.com/suxrobgm</a> LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/suxrobgm">https://www.facebook.com/suxrobgm</a>

GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/suxrobGM">https://github.com/suxrobGM</a>



## **Profile**

Thinking "out of the box" to provide software-based solutions

Strong in design and integration problem-solving skills. Expert in C#, .NET, and T-SQL with database analysis and design. Skilled in developing business plans, requirements specifications, user documentation, and architectural systems research. Strong written and verbal communications.

#### Software skills include:

- Languages: C#, C/C++, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, XML, SQL, Lua
- Databases: MS SQL, PostgreSQL, Access, MySQL
- Software: Visual Studio, Rider, DataGrip, Visual Studio Code, DotPeek
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front end public and internal websites as well as challenging back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Coding, testing and fixing programming errors.
- Collaborate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

## Work experience

#### Freelancer.com

#### **Freelance Software Developer**

02/2019 – present

- Web Designing and Web Development.
- Worked closely with client to provide a customized website for their business.
- Design and development of various websites.
- Designing and maintaining front end for web and mobile applications.
- Writing unit tests to improve code predictability and documentation.
- Develop support tools to reduce working time from hours to minutes.
- Used coding methods in specific programming languages to initiate and improve program execution and functionality.

#### EC Dev Team • Uzbekistan

#### **Team Lead**

07/2016 - 02/2019

- Managing developers team
- Designing game Al logic
- Programming game mechanics
- Scripting game map
- Programming developers tools
- Balancing game's difficulty.
- Watching on process developing game in a team.
- Ability of enhance and optimize data for match with many devices.

### **Education**

## Tashkent University of Information Technologies Samarkand • Uzbekistan

#### Software engineering

09/2017 - 06/2019

• Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

## INTI International University & Colleges Kuala-Lumpur • Malaysia

#### **Computer Science**

08/2019 - present

• American Degree Transfer Program

#### **Awards**

# **1st place in Individual ACM ICPC format contest Tashkent University of Information Technologies**

12/2017

• Winner in individual ACM ICPC format contest between TUIT students

## **Top-10 team in IT Universities contest in Uzbekistan Tashkent University of Information Technologies**

02/2018

 My team was in the list of top 10 teams in contest between IT Universities in Uzbekistan

## **Strengths**

Ability to learn from mistakes • Creative thinking • Confident • Critical thinking • Working quickly • Accuracy • Solving complex problems

### **Skills**

#### **Programming Languages**

Python ■■■□□

JavaScript **TEMP** 

TypeScript ■■■□□

Java ■■□□□

PHP ■■□□□

HTML/CSS ■■■■■

SQL **THE S** 

Lua ■■□□□

### Frameworks & Technologies

.NET

ASP.NET ■■■■■

WPF

Xamarin.Forms ■■■■□

React ■■■□□

Qt ■■■□□

Unity 3D ■■□□□

ML.NET

Entity Framework

Unit Testing ■■■□

Bootstrap 4

Git **EEEE** 

ADO.NET

jQuery ■■■■

### **Publications**

#### **Introducing .NET 5**

http://www.suxrobgm.net/Blog/Introducing-NET-5

05/2019

Introduction to Microsft's new technology .NET 5

#### ML.NET - Machine Learning for .NET

http://www.suxrobgm.net/Blog/Announcing-ML.NET

05/2019

At Finally! Microsoft announced ML.NET 1.0

### **Certificates**

Certified Scrum Master - Agile Alliance

License 544689

2016

### **Open Source**

**Github** - contributions in project Server Side Analytics https://github.com/matteofabbri/ServerSideAnalytics

Stackoverflow - reputation 15000+ top 3%